人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
你被监视着
You are being watched.
■
・ 翻译  阿好
・ 翻译  茶炒栗子
■
・ 翻译  惠子
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
■
・ 翻译  卫老哥
・ 翻译  王小麦
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
■
翻  幸田实果子
译  面条打包子
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
■
・ 校对  阿好
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
■
压制  灰灰是菇凉
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
阿包  烟幕迟迟  阿包  烟幕迟迟  阿包  烟幕迟迟  阿包  烟幕迟迟  阿包  烟幕迟迟  阿包  烟幕迟迟
■
时间轴
政府认为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
我们不
We don't.
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
特效
灰灰
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
总监
阿好
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第三季 第四集
动物医护中心
他不肯吃东西  整天睡觉
He won't eat. He sleeps all day.
偶尔醒了就吐
When he's not throwing up.
你们最近换了他的饮食了吗
Have you changed his food?
一直是高档的粗磨谷物
Just the same high-performance kibble,
偶尔加点儿剩饭
plus the occasional table scrap.
我从不喂他剩饭
I never feed him from the table.
嗜睡  呕吐  食欲不振
Lethargy, vomiting, and lack of appetite
意味着可能有更严重的病因
could indicate a more serious underlying cause.
我得安排进一步检查
I'd like to order some additional tests.
什么都行
Whatever he needs.
现在  我先开点止吐药
In the meantime, I have some anti-nausea medicine
缓解下他的症状
that should ease his symptoms.
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
抱歉  你不能进来
I'm sorry, you can't be in here.
他们也不能
Neither can they.
交出[麻醉剂]克他命  饶你一命
Give us the ketamine, the doctor lives.
你真不该来这手
You shouldn't have done that.
你们是谁
Who are you?
我们不过是一对养狗人
We're merely a couple of concerned dog owners,
詹森医生
Dr. Jensen.
我不知道要如何感谢你们
I don't know how to thank you.
你接待处出售的那些昂贵的咀嚼玩具
One of those expensive chew toys you have for sale at reception
就挺好
would help.
小熊喜欢他的新兽医
Bear likes his new vet.
他还有一个月就要接种疫苗了
He's due for vaccinations in a month.
不妨来詹森医生这里
It might be nice to visit Dr. Jensen
而不用他参加卧底行动
when he's not participating in a covert operation.
拜托帮帮我  我丈夫失踪了
Please, help me. I've lost my husband.
音频拦截
911报警电话
我在船上  在长岛海湾
I'm out on our boat, on Long Island Sound.
那你丈夫呢
And where is your husband?
我睡觉前他还在
He was here when I fell asleep.
我们有个新号码了  里瑟先生
We have a new number, Mr. Reese.
凡妮莎・沃特金斯
Vanessa Watkins.
前地检官办公室的公诉人
Former prosecutor with the district attorney's office.
她起诉过城里最凶残的暴力罪犯
She's put away some of the city's worst violent offenders,
强奸犯  杀人犯  毒枭
rapists, murderers, drug traffickers.
她嫁给了杰里米・沃特金斯  辩护律师
Married to Jeremy Watkins, the defense attorney.
公诉人嫁给了辩护律师
A prosecutor married to a defense attorney?
本是天敌啊  里瑟先生
Cats and Dogs, Mr. Reese.
杰里米的辩护能力帮一堆刑事嫌犯逍遥法外
Jeremy's helped countless alleged criminals walk on technicalities,
不过现在看起来有麻烦的是他
But it appears now he's the one in trouble.
杰出的辩护律师海上失踪
他在海上失踪两天了
He's been missing at sea for two days.
海岸警卫队还在搜寻他
Coast Guard's still looking for him.
也许某位心怀怨恨的客户回来找他算账了
Maybe an unhappy client came back to haunt him.
看到凡妮莎了  芬奇
Got eyes on Vanessa, Finch.
复制手机
凡妮莎・沃特金斯
跟个朋友在一起
Has a friend with her.
一切都会好起来的
Everything is gonna be all right.
你无法确定  妮可
You don't know that, Nicole.
妮可・斯宾塞  从大学起就是凡妮莎的至友
Nicole Spencer, Vanessa's best friend since college.
她在安慰她
She's consoling her.
芬奇  凡妮莎另有麻烦了
Finch, Vanessa's got another problem.
沃特金斯夫人  纽约警察
Ms. Watkins. NYPD.
你被捕了  涉嫌谋杀你丈夫
You're under arrest for the murder of your husband,
杰里米・沃特金斯
Jeremy Watkins.
看来杰里米已经不再"失踪"了
Guess Jeremy's not missing anymore.
警察认为她杀了他
Cops think she killed him.
天啊
Oh, dear.
手背过来
Hands behind your back.
机器是不是把她的号码给迟了
Did the machine give us her number too late?
不
No.
机器给出凡妮莎的号码
The machine generated Vanessa's number
是在杰里米失踪后
after Jeremy's disappearance.
是新威胁  即将到来
The threat is new and imminent.
这样的话  我们得监听她的审讯
In that case, we need to get ears on her interrogation.
走吧
Let's go.
凡妮莎・沃特金斯
Vanessa Watkins.
我从没想过你也会坐在这里
Never thought I'd see you on that side of the table.
你很顽强  我以前很喜欢你
You were tough. I liked you.
见鬼  我甚至很尊重你
Hell, I even respected you,
直到你嫁给了那个锦衣华服巧舌如簧的混球
Till you married that silver-tongued slimeball in the $5,000 suit.
我认为像沃特金斯夫人这样经验丰富的公诉人
I would have thought a seasoned prosecutor like Ms. Watkins
会马上要求律师
would invoke her right to an attorney.
没事的  保持沉默
It's okay, keep quiet.
你的求救电话能替你说话
Your SOS call will do the talking for you.
拜托帮帮我  我丈夫失踪了
Please, help me. I've lost my husband.
我在船上  在长岛海湾
I'm out on our boat, on Long Island Sound.
那你丈夫呢
And where is your husband?
我睡觉前他还在
He was here when I fell asleep,
但我听到有声音  我走到甲板上
But I heard a noise, and when I got to the deck,
看到他的尸体漂走了
I saw his body floating away.
拜托  帮帮我
Please, help me.
我差点就相信了你"无助女子"的那套表演
I almost bought your whole "Damsel In Distress" act.
你丈夫的血
Your husband's blood.
你是唯一在甲板上的人
You were the only other person on board,
所以我们检测了你在海岸警卫队签过字的陈述
So we tested the statement you signed for the Coast Guard,
你在上边作证说你丈夫掉落海里了
the one where you swore your husband fell overboard.
知道我们发现了什么吗
Know what we found?
射击残留  没错
Gunshot residue. Yeah.
你忘记洗手了
You forgot to wash your hands.
金钱会让人大意
Money makes people careless.
你丈夫一死  你就能拿到一大笔
With your husband gone, you got a lot more of it.
五百万的人寿保险金  还有度假别墅在
5 mil life insurance, vacation home in, uh,
在什么地方来着
Wha--what was it again,
[意大利]托斯卡纳
Tuscany, hmm?
无所谓了  反正你再也见不到了
Doesn't matter, you're never gonna see it again.
为什么呢
Why?
因为我们找到枪了
'Cause we found the gun,
你用来杀死杰里米的枪
The gun you used to kill Jeremy.
目击者看见你扔到了长岛海湾
Witness saw you toss it into the Long Island Sound,
所以我们去打捞了
So we dragged it.
费了点儿时间  不过我们捞上来了
Took a while, but we fished it out.
要我说  你算做了件好事
Ask me, you did the world a favor,
搞死了你的混蛋丈夫
ridding it of that scumbag husband of yours.
告诉我们到底发生了什么
Tell us what really happened.
我们来个协议
We'll hammer out a deal.
这么多的间接证据
Such a damning list of circumstantial evidence.
你干嘛还要逼我招供呢  卡梅伦警探
So why are you pressing me for a confession, Detective Cameron?
你没找到尸体  是吧
You don't have a body, do you?
现在可以请我的律师进来了
You can show my attorney in now.
感谢前来
Thanks for coming.
我挺惊讶你居然会叫我
I was surprised you asked for me,
毕竟你可曾对我老板说过我是
Considering you once told my boss I was
"集懒惰和无能于一身的极品"
"A unique combination of lazy and ineffectual."
我的律师跟我之间的谈话
The conversation my attorney and I are about to have
是受保护的
will be privileged.
把摄像头关掉
I want all cameras removed.
法官们都在家里享受白兰地和雪茄呢
The judges are all home with their brandy and cigars,
这就意味着你要被关一晚上了
which means you get to spend the night in lockup.
抱歉了  警探  请离开这房间
Sorry, Detective, we gotta clear the room.
听起来像是凡妮莎枪杀了她丈夫
Sounds like Vanessa shot her husband.
她还是清白的  直到被证明有罪
She's innocent until proven guilty.
或者直到她的律师找到漏洞
Or until her lawyer finds a loophole.
沃特金斯夫人非常聪明  她先不要求律师
Ms. Watkins was smart enough not to ask for her attorney
等着卡梅伦警探把整个案子和盘托出
until she'd heard Detective Cameron's entire case against her.
她清楚  没有尸体
She knows that, without a body,
他需要她招供了才能立案上法庭
he needs a confession to bolster his case to the jury.
卡梅伦想关到她开口
Cameron's trying to keep her in custody until she talks.
身为公诉人
For a prosecutor,
被关一晚上都可能有生命危险
a single night in lockup could be life-threatening.
我们得把她弄出来
We need to get her out of there.
喂
Yeah?
警探  凡妮莎还在跟她的律师谈吗
Detective, is Vanessa still speaking with her attorney?
凡妮莎的律师刚走
Vanessa's attorney just left.
我们要你把沃特金斯夫人带出关押室
We need you to get Ms. Watkins out of custody.
有点儿晚了
A little late for that.
凡妮莎敲倒了她的律师
Vanessa knocked her attorney out cold,
换了她的衣服  直接走了
took her clothes, and walked right out of here.
难怪她非要莎拉・埃利斯
No wonder she requested Sarah Ellis.
我肯定她们两个
I'd be willing to wager they're
年龄  体重  身形都相似
similar in age, height, and build.
凡妮莎逃了  她还是杀人嫌犯
So Vanessa's escaped, and she's an alleged murderer.
也许机器给出她的号码是因为她还要继续
Maybe the machine gave us her number because she isn't finished.
好了  都给我听着
All right, listen up.
区域警觉系统拍到了嫌犯的录像
Domain Awareness captured footage of the suspect,
凡妮莎・沃特金斯  买了一张去费城的巴士车票
Vanessa Watkins, buying a bus ticket to Philadelphia.
文件应该已经发到你们邮箱里了
The file should be in your inbox now.
这位逃犯的巴士将在一小时内出发
Our fugitive's bus leaves in less than an hour.
她登不上车  因为我们会阻止她
She will not be on it because we will stop her!
我收到录像了  谢谢  警探
I received the footage. Thank you, Detective.
走吧
Come on.
拿到坐标了吗
You got the coordinates?
车站西南方五条街范围内
Five-block radius on the southwest side of the station.
我记录了所有的公用电话和自动取款机
I made a note of every pay phone and ATM.
干得好
Nice work.
谢谢
Thanks.
不  你根本没听我说
No, you're not listening to me.
我跟你说过
Like I told you before...
这正是我要告诉你的
That's what I tried to tell you.
铁尼警探似乎有点儿  紧张
Detective Terney seems a little, uh, intense.
建议下怎么跟他相处吧
And advice on how to get along with him?
警队里有些人
Some people on the force,
你最好离远一点儿
you're better off keeping your distance.
不太明白你说什么
Not sure I get what you mean.
你会明白的
You will.
芬奇
Finch,
凡妮莎不在巴士站
no sign of Vanessa at the bus station.
我想我知道为什么
I think I might know why.
身为公诉人  沃特金斯夫人应该清楚
As a prosecutor, Ms. Watkins would know
城市监控网络的范围
the extent of the city's surveillance network.
她完全可以避开摄像头
She could have avoided the cameras altogether?
正是  但她没有  她直视了摄像头
That's just it, she doesn't. She looks right at them.
她是故意被摄像头捕捉到的
She got caught on camera on purpose.
她根本无意乘坐巴士
She has no intention of getting on that bus.
沃特金斯夫人已经证明了自己
Ms. Watkins has already proven herself
熟练的骗术技巧
practiced at the art of deception.
她让我想起你了  里瑟先生
She's beginning to remind me of you, Mr. Reese.
我让肖女士重走凡妮莎的路线
I'll have Ms. Shaw retrace Vanessa's steps.
凡妮莎离开车站前
Vanessa seems to have picked the pocket of an old man
掏了一位穿橙色夹克的老人的东西
in an orange jacket before she left the station.
你有没有看出迹象
Have you seen anything that would give you an indication
她要去哪儿
where she was going?
没有
Nope.
不过录像上那位老人回来了
But the old man from the footage is back.
我去问问他
I'm gonna ask him.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你丢东西了吗
Did you lose something?
-钱包吗  -没有
- A wallet maybe? - No.
但我找不到手机了
But I did misplace my cell phone.
要是你把号码给我
If you give me the number,
我有朋友可以追踪
I know somebody who can track it.
给
There you go.
芬奇  这里满眼看去只有毒贩
Finch, drug dealers are the only traffic we're seeing out here.
那就再看看
You might want to have another look.
复制手机
强制配对
完成
我来找混响
I'm here to see reverb.
混响已经有约了
Reverb's got a prior engagement.
我建议你走你的
I suggest you move along.
雷金纳德  你能听到吗
Reginald! Can you hear me?
只有两个人可以喊我雷金纳德
Only two people allowed to call me Reginald.
我妈和法庭
My moms and the courts.
芬奇  我发给你一张照片
Finch, I'm sending you a photo.
这人名叫雷金纳德
Guy's first name is Reginald.
毒贩假释出狱
"混响"雷金纳德・马歇尔
Reginald "Reverb" Marshall.
判刑二十年  刚刚被提前放出
Recently released after serving part of a 20-year sentence
罪名是谋杀和贩毒
for murder and drug trafficking.
是凡妮莎起诉的
Vanessa put him away.
那她现在为什么来找他
So why is she visiting him now?
谢谢你为我向法官求情
Thanks for talking to that judge for me,
放我出来
getting me out.
芬奇  通知你一声
Finch, wanted to let you know.
有消息了
Tip came through.
有人发现凡妮莎
Someone spotted Vanessa
出现在华盛顿高地一栋毒贩的建筑里
at a dealer's building in Washington Heights.
感谢你的通知  警探
I appreciate that update, Detective.
卡梅伦警探提醒我们说嫌犯可能
Detective Cameron's instructed us to consider the suspect
持有武器  很危险
armed and dangerous.
这是标准流程吗
Is that standard operating procedure?
不是  并没有证据显示嫌犯有武器
Not when there's no evidence the suspect has a weapon.
我认识凡妮莎
I knew Vanessa.
跟她合作过几个案子  她很顽强
Worked a couple cases together. She was tough.
不知道为什么  反正卡梅伦非要抓住她
Don't know why, but Cameron's determined to bring her in,
死活不论
dead or alive.
混响刚刚给了凡妮莎一袋货
Reginald just gave Vanessa a brick of coke.
前公诉人准备
What's a former prosecutor planning to do
拿一公斤可卡因干什么呢
with a kilogram of cocaine?
干非法的事
Something illegal.
里瑟先生  警察在路上了
Mr. Reese, police are on the way.
你和肖女士得马上离开
You and Ms. Shaw need to vacate the premises.
我让卡特警探帮忙掩护下
I'll ask Detective Carter to run interference.
要我帮你搞定谁
You need me to take care of someone for you,
一个电话就行
just call me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我要彻查整栋建筑  层层清理  快
I want that building cleared, floor by floor, now!
遵命长官
Yes, Sir!
喂
Yeah?
我获取了沃特金斯夫人
I've accessed the provider system
手机供应商的权限
for the cellular phone Ms. Watkins acquired.
卡梅伦已经发现她了
Cameron's already spotted her.
他正在搜查整栋建筑
He's searching the building now.
我帮你省点儿麻烦吧
Let me save you some trouble.
我已经打开了载波相位跟踪
I was able to turn on the carrier phase tracking
手机的位置定位误差十五厘米
and determine the phone's position to within 6 inches.
她在屋顶西南角
She's at the southwest corner of the roof.
其他人检查屋顶
The rest of you check the roof!
跟我来  我可以帮你
Come with me. I can help you.
没人帮得了我
No one can help me.
但我发誓  我没杀我丈夫
But I swear, I did not kill my husband.
不  等等
No! Wait!
凡妮莎告诉我她没杀她丈夫
Vanessa told me she didn't kill her husband.
你认为她是清白的吗
Do you think she's innocent?
我不确定
I don't know.
但那一刻  我认为她说的是实情
But in that moment, I thought she was telling the truth.
那看来这位前公诉人不相信系统
I guess the former prosecutor doesn't trust the system, then.
要是系统永远正确
Think I'd be standing here in a uniform
我能落到穿制服这地步吗
if the system always worked?
卡梅伦警探下令说
Detective Cameron ordered us
凡妮莎持有武器  很危险
to consider Vanessa armed and dangerous.
卡梅伦是HR的人
Is Cameron HR?
我也在怀疑
I wondered the same thing,
但我打探了一下  原来
But I asked around, and turns out,
杰里米・沃特金斯有个客户  涉嫌谋杀
Jeremy Watkins had a client, alleged murderer.
杰里米在庭上把卡梅伦说成有种族歧视的骗子
Jeremy made Cameron out to be a racist liar on the stand.
被告无罪释放
The defendant walked,
而那个任由卡梅伦出丑的公诉人
and the prosecutor who let Cameron get hung out to dry?
凡妮莎・沃特金斯
Vanessa Watkins.
卡梅伦不是HR的人
Cameron isn't HR.
抓着凡妮莎让她付出代价  这是私仇
Catching Vanessa and making her pay--it's personal.
谢了
Thanks.
抱歉
Sorry.
下次我在车里等着
Next time, I'll wait in the car.
凡妮莎宁愿跳楼
Vanessa would rather jump off a building
也不愿被卡梅伦抓住
than have Cameron take her in.
坏人总是逃
Bad guys always run.
所谓好人也一样
As do the so-called good guys,
只要后边有警探不论死活地追捕
when the detective pursuing them wants them dead or alive.
我在想  沃特金斯夫人会是受害人吗
I wonder, could Ms. Watkins be a victim after all?
走
Off.
乖
Good boy.
卡特认为她可能是清白的
Carter thinks she could be innocent.
我还是押凡妮莎杀了她丈夫
My money's still on Vanessa killing her husband.
你要赌吗
You want to put it to a bet?
一百块如何
How about 100 bucks?
我们不赌号码
We really don't wager on whether our numbers
是受害人还是行凶者
are victims or perpetrators.
你们俩做这个多久了
You guys have been doing this for how long,
就没有一次想着赌赌结果
and not once did you think to bet on the outcome?
随便你以为我们俩有何不道德的行为
Regardless of your rather louche take on what we do here,
肖女士  问题还是存在
Ms. Shaw, the question remains,
如果凡妮莎没有杀死她的丈夫
if Vanessa didn't kill her husband,
那是谁  跟她现在的危机又有何关系
who did, and what has that to do with her present jeopardy?
我不知道  不过我们得找到她
I don't know, but we need to find her.
>失去信号<
她扔掉我们追踪的手机了
She's disposed of the cell phone we were tracking.
纽约警察现在肯定冻结了她的账号
NYPD must have frozen her accounts by now.
她需要钱
She'll need money.
那袋货能帮她搞到
Brick of coke she has could help with that.
你以为沃特金斯夫人计划贩毒
Do you think Ms. Watkins plans to traffic cocaine?
如果是的话  她需要帮助
If she does, she'll need help.
人在逃亡时总是会犯一种错误
People on the run always make the same mistake,
跟熟人联系
contact someone they know.
凡妮莎被捕时跟个朋友在一起
Vanessa was with a friend when she was arrested.
妮可・斯宾塞
Nicole Spencer.
妮可今天主持个读书会
And Nicole is hosting a book club today,
尽管凡妮莎已陷入如此窘境
in spite of Vanessa's predicament.
有哪位女士无法出席吗
Any of these ladies not gonna make it?
这位明迪写着"也许"
This Mindy is a maybe.
"也许"就是"不出席"
Maybe means no.
我以她朋友的身份去
I'll go as her friend.
你确定自己合适吗
Are you sure you'll fit in?
当然
Of course.
我有秘密武器
I have a secret weapon.
我来参加读书会
I'm here for book club.
我是明迪的朋友  卡门
I'm Mindy's friend, Carmen.
明迪这周来不了
Mindy couldn't make it this week.
我们正有位朋友
And we actually have a friend
经历不幸
who's going through a rough time.
真遗憾
That's a shame.
我不知道要拿这些夏敦埃怎么办了
I don't know what I'll do with all this chardonnay.
杰里米在法庭上简直像斗牛  但他深爱凡妮莎
Jeremy was a pit bull in court, but he doted on Vanessa,
任她予取予求
gave her anything she wanted.
谁会想到她那么不开心呢
Who would have thought she was so unhappy?
有财富  有魅力  有容貌
Wealthy, charismatic, good looks to match?
那种男人管不住的
A man like that is hard to pin down.
奥利维亚  拜托
Olivia, please.
别让明迪的朋友以为我们就是在一起八卦的
Let's not make Mindy's friend think we're just here to gossip.
盥洗室在哪儿
Where's your powder room?
能否问下读书会进展如何
Do I dare ask how the book club is going?
一群主妇冒充知识分子装模作样
Bunch of pseudo-intellectual glorified trophy wives.
行了  我避开了
Okay, so I ducked out,
登入妮可的银行账户
logged in to Nicole's bank account.
她没暗中给凡妮莎钱
She is not sneaking money to Vanessa.
凡妮莎跟她联系过吗
Has Vanessa made contact?
充电中
复制手机
妮可・斯宾塞
强制配对
完成
看看吧
Take a look.
这是妮可的手机
We're up on Nicole's phone.
看来沃特金斯夫人并没有
Doesn't appear that Ms. Watkins
联系她的至友
has reached out to her best friend.
美人  想你了
真有意思  我正躺在床上想你呢
你穿了什么
没穿
只有你最爱的内裤
脱了
脱下来
给我看
自己来看嘛
我看到大多数短信来自一位男性朋友
The majority of the texts I see are from a male friend,
你穿了什么
没穿
只有你最爱的内裤
脱了
脱下来
给我看
自己来看嘛
描述得栩栩如生
and they're of rather a graphic nature.
妮可有男朋友
Nicole's got a boyfriend?
对  名叫"火辣"
Yes, named "Hot stuff".
反向查找号码
搜索中...
天啊
Oh, dear.
《洛丽塔》的作者
纳博科夫以极富挑战性的笔法
Nabokov faced some unique challenges
真实地书写了那种禁忌之爱
writing so honestly about forbidden love.
说到禁忌之爱
Speaking of forbidden love,
是你故意陷害凡妮莎谋杀杰里米
Did you frame Vanessa for Jeremy's murder
因为你跟他睡了
because you were sleeping with him?
抱歉
Sorry.
不是杰里米  是"火辣"
Not Jeremy. "Hot stuff".
我没  我
I didn't--I--
要我能做主  就直接给你一枪
Up to me, I'd shoot your sorry ass.
可惜的是  不行
Unfortunately, it's not,
所以我不得不保护你  因为你的至友
So I have to protect you, because your best friend
也许正在来杀你的路上
might be on her way here to kill you.
现在
Now...
这本书讲什么的
what's this book about?
我又看了一下凡妮莎的档案
I took another look at Vanessa's file.
证据感觉就是不对劲
The evidence just wasn't sitting right with me.
怎么说
How so?
凡妮莎手上的射击残留
The GSR on Vanessa's hands.
法医在甲板上只发现一点点
Forensics found trace amounts all over the deck,
而浓度最高的地方
but the largest concentration?
是凡妮莎的化妆品
On Vanessa's cosmetics.
所以要不就是凡妮莎枪杀她丈夫后
So either Vanessa shot her husband
马上擦了眼影
and then put on eye shadow...
要不那射击残留就是栽赃的
Or the gunshot residue was planted.
那个帮警察
What's the name of the witness
找到枪的目击者叫什么
who helped the police find the gun?
斯科特・罗林斯
Scott Rawlins.
他在沃特金斯夫妻游船的停泊码头工作
He works at the marina where the Watkins kept their yacht.
我去跟他聊聊
I'll have a talk with him.
船真不错
Nice boat.
虽说人家在托斯卡纳有房子
Even for people with a place in Tuscany.
华盛顿高地那人是谁
Who was that man in Washington Heights,
穿西装那个
in the suit?
我们是成年人了
Look, we're adults.
我不用知道你的一切
I don't have to know everything about you,
你也不用知道我的一切
you don't have to know everything about me.
我认为你能继续生活挺好
I think it's good you're moving on.
你说什么
Excuse me?
忘掉比彻
From Beecher.
重新约会挺好的
Good for you for seeing someone new.
是啊  谢了
Yeah. Thanks.
我也有未婚妻
I got a fiancee myself.
她想私奔
Course, she'd rather elope.
而我想办场超大的派对
Me, I want the blow-out party,
所有亲友都到场
all my friends and family there.
你未婚妻  她家人很多吗
Your fiancee, she from a big family?
不  她和她家人其实不太亲近
No, she's not real close to her folks.
也许她正因为这才不想办派对
Probably why she doesn't want the big party.
谢了  卡特
Thanks, Carter.
没事儿
No problem.
你和国际刑警的线人联系过没
Did you talk to your contact at interpol?
沃特金斯的那条游艇
The yacht the Watkins owned--
价值五百万  但是呢
valued at 5 mil, but get this,
它被全额抵押了
it's leveraged to the hilt
而且马上就要被贷方收回了
and about to be repossessed by the lender,
而贷方是黑帮开的空壳公司
A shell corporation that belongs to a mobster.
杰里米・沃特金斯欠黑帮五百万美元
Jeremy Watkins owed a mobster $5 million?
至少五百万
At least.
杰里米的账户都负债了
All of Jeremy's accounts were in the red,
除了一个
except for one,
一个叫"重获清白"的慈善基金
a charity by the name of "Innocence Now".
每名被告都应该有机会证实自己的清白
那个账户在哪里开的  警探
Where is this account based, Detective?
康涅狄格州的格林威治
Greenwich, Connecticut.
看来我要去格林威治了吧
I guess I'm going to Greenwich.
如果你不介意的话
If you wouldn't mind.
我相信肖女士已经
I'm sure Ms. Shaw has had
喝够夏敦埃也读够纳博科夫了
enough Chardonnay and Nabokov for one afternoon.
我会让她也过去
I'll have her join you.
里瑟先生  杰里米・沃特金斯欠了
Mr. Reese, Jeremy Watkins was deeply in debt
黑帮一大笔钱
to an organized crime affiliate.
很有可能是他们杀了杰里米
It's entirely possible that they killed Jeremy.
如果他们知道他不还钱
If they knew he would never pay,
也许会杀了他  给凡妮莎传达信息
they could have killed him to send a message to Vanessa.
是的  不还钱就得死
Yes, "Pay up or else!"
沃特金斯夫人越来越像受害人了
Ms. Watkins is beginning to look more and more like a victim,
但我还是不明白为什么受害人
although I can't explain why a victim would procure
需要那么多可卡因
such a large amount of cocaine.
也许我明白
I think I can.
我刚找到指证凡妮莎的证人
I just found the witness against Vanessa.
斯科特・罗林斯
Scott Rawlins.
也许是他杀了杰里米  扔了枪
Perhaps he dumped the gun that killed Jeremy.
能找他问问那份栽赃的证据吗
Were you able to ask him about the planted evidence?
不行  因为有人刚栽赃了他
No, because someone just planted evidence on him.
芬奇  警察刚逮捕了
Finch, the cops just arrested
斯科特・罗林斯  罪名是藏毒并试图贩卖
Scott Rawlins for possession with intent to sell.
证物是一块可卡因
Had a brick of cocaine identical
和雷金纳德给凡妮莎的一模一样
to the one Reginald gave Vanessa.
她栽赃了指证她的证人来破坏他的可信度
She planted drugs on the witness against her to discredit him.
换我也会这么做
Exactly what I would have done.
这样的话  我还是不知道
In that case, I still can't speak
她到底是受害人还是行凶者了
to whether she's a victim or a perpetrator.
凡妮莎知道
But Vanessa can.
她留了下来欣赏她的成果
She stuck around to admire her own work.
先栽赃  再偷人家的车逃走
Frame a man up, then steal his car to get away.
厉害啊  凡妮莎  我们得谈谈了
You're good, Vanessa. We need to talk.
刚问过里瑟先生  他们还有十五分钟就到
I just spoke to Mr. Reese. They're 15 minutes away.
你确定这是个好主意吗
Are you sure this is a good idea?
我觉得  最好是先确定
It seems to me, the best way to start
沃特金斯夫人是否
would be to ascertain Ms. Watkins'
杀了她的丈夫
guilt or innocence in the death of her husband.
然后  我们才能弄清楚
From there, we can attempt to figure out
现在的情况
the current situation.
要是肖女士在这儿  她会愿意加倍下注
Ms. Shaw were here, she'd be willing to wager double or nothing
押凡妮莎是威胁
that Vanessa's the threat.
那么如果凡妮莎有罪  我们就把她交给
So Vanessa's guilty, we turn her over
一个想要杀了她的腐败警察吗
to a corrupt cop who might be trying to kill her?
如果她是清白的  我们放她走
And if she's innocent, we let her go free,
而即使如此  也许是她想要杀人
at which point, she may still be trying to kill somebody.
我们得两害权其轻
We need to figure out which flawed plan is best.
我有个主意
I can help with that.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
你们是谁
Who are you people?
现在  沃特金斯夫人
As of this moment, Ms. Watkins,
我们是你的法官和陪审团
we are your judge and jury.
你在此做己方陈述
You're here to make your argument.
你们现在至少犯了三项重罪
I can name at least three felonies you're committing.
绑架  非法拘禁  胁迫
Kidnapping, unlawful imprisonment, coercion!
我为什么要对你们做陈述
Why should I make my argument to you?
因为如果我们判定你没有
Because if we decide that you're innocent
杀死你丈夫
of your husband's murder,
我们可以给你一个新身份
we can provide you with an alternate identity
让你在新城市开始新生活
and a fresh start in a new city.
如果你有罪  我们就把你交给纽约警察
If you're guilty, we turn you over to the NYPD.
我记得你
I remember you.
你在凶案组工作
You worked Homicide.
纽约警察局里有一堆黑警
NYPD is full of dirty cops.
这不用你说
Don't have to tell me that.
但我认为你不是
But I don't think you're one of them.
所以你们这场审判
So this trial you want to have...
我参加
I'm game.
监控录像显示逃犯
Surveillance footage clocked our fugitive
大约在八十分钟前上了这辆越野车
getting into this SUV approximately 80 minutes ago.
她有朋友帮忙  男性
She's got a friend, male.
穿着西装
Appears to be wearing a suit.
分析仪在寻找这辆车
Plate readers are on the lookout for the car.
在码头拉起警戒线
Set up a perimeter around the marina.
关闭大桥
Close off the bridges.
找出所有他们见过  聊过  想过的人  快
Find anyone who's seen them, talked to them, thought about them, now!
甲板上有你丈夫的血
Your husband's blood on the deck,
射击残留在你手上
GSR on your hands--
还有我的化妆品里
And on my cosmetics.
你读了警方报告
You read the police report.
我溜出警局时从卡梅伦桌上顺走了一份
I swiped a copy from Cameron's desk on my way out of the station.
你不会吗
Wouldn't you?
或许会
Probably.
我丈夫不是被谋杀的
My husband wasn't murdered.
他是溺水
He drowned.
有人栽赃了证据陷害我
Someone planted that evidence and framed me.
证明
Prove it.
我是辩方  列举证据是你的工作
I'm the defense. Burden of proof lies with you.
你可以反对
You can object.
好吧  我反对
Fine, I object.
反对无效
Overruled.
我在斯科特・罗林斯的储物柜里找到了这个
I found this in Scott Rwlins' locker.
在你栽赃证据的时候
When you planted the drugs?
是的  五万美元
Yes. $50,000.
一个码头警卫一年也赚不了这么多钱
A marina guard doesn't make that in a year.
有人花钱雇他栽赃证据
Someone paid him to plant the evidence,
告诉警察去哪里找那把枪
tell the police where to find that gun.
就是陷害我的那个人做的
The same person who is framing me.
你没法证明这笔钱的来路
You have no chain of custody for that money.
它可能来自任何地方
It could have come from anywhere.
什...
Wh--
你曾经负责抓坏人
You used to put bad guys away.
后来却嫁给了辩护律师
Then you married a defense attorney,
他帮助杀人犯逍遥法外  臭名昭著
one notorious for helping murderers walk.
你为什么会换边站
Why'd you switch sides like that?
因为钱吗
Was it the money?
我第一次起诉凶案
My first murder trial,
我完全不知所措
I was a wreck.
每天晚上都对着镜子练习
Rehearsing every night in the mirror,
想象陪审团穿着内衣的样子
picturing the jury in their underwear,
所有的把戏都试过
all the old tricks.
我眼看要赢了
I was winning...
但是被告换了一位新律师
until the defendant hired new counsel.
杰里米
Jeremy.
他打得我惨败
He trounced me.
但之后他很友好
But he was kind afterwards.
告诉我我很勇敢
Told me I had grit.
要是他在就不会让卡梅伦这么对我
He wouldn't have let Cameron hunt me down like this.
杰里米会保护我
Jeremy would have protected me.
他背了黑帮一屁股债时可没保护你
He wasn't protecting you when he ran up all that debt to a mobster.
但现在他死了
But now that he's dead,
他的人寿保险可以偿还所有债务
that life insurance policy will wipe out all his debt,
你最后还会会有盈余
and you'll finally be in the black.
杰里米和我有一个生前信托
Jeremy and I had a living trust.
其中的条款规定
That agreement stipulates that
如果他死得可疑
if he died under suspicious circumstances,
我一分钱都拿不到
I wouldn't see a penny,
我也不会拿
and I won't.
所有的钱都会进我们的慈善基金
Everything is going to our charity.
重获清白
Innocence Now.
你是那个账户的联署人吗  沃特金斯夫人
Are you a cosigner on that account, Ms. Watkins?
可能是吧  我也不知道
I might be. I-I don't know.
所有的文书工作都是杰里米弄的
Jeremy took care of all the paperwork.
如果所有的文书工作都是杰里米弄的
If Jeremy took care of all the paperwork,
那你怎么知道那笔债务的
how did you know about the debt?
我在车上发现一张恐吓字条
I found a threatening note on my car,
就在杰里米死的前几晚
a few nights before Jeremy died.
我们本该有一个浪漫的晚餐
We were supposed to be having a romantic dinner,
但是我在游艇上质问杰里米
but I confronted Jeremy on the yacht.
我们吵架了
We argued.
我去游艇下层  想冷静一下
I went below deck to just clear my head.
等我回来的时候  杰里米不见了
When I came back up, Jeremy was gone.
我对我丈夫说的最后一句话是
The last thing I said to my husband was
我很后悔嫁给他
I was sorry that we ever got married.
但我不是真心的
But I didn't mean it,
我也没杀他
and I didn't kill him.
你们一定要相信我
You have to believe me.
欢迎来到康涅狄格
那个账户名字叫什么来着
What was the account name again?
重获清白
Innocence Now.
看来不是我的密码  是吧
That's not my password, now is it?
喂
Yeah.
警探  你们有没有查出沃特金斯夫人
Detective, would you be able to tell me if Ms. Watkins
是否是"重获清白"的账户联署人
is a cosigner on the Innocence Now account?
还没有
Not yet.
格林威治这边做事儿慢半拍
They do things a little slow here in Greenwich.
不妙啊
That's not good.
小圈圈转啊转的
The little wheel's spinning.
我  重启啊
I'll just, uh, restart.
我先挂了
I gotta go.
就算是你  扎老人也太刷新下限了
Even for you, stabbing a senior would be a new low.
你知道个屁
You don't know that.
"重获清白"的账户上
The Innocence Now account had a balance
昨天还有两千万美元余额
of just over $20 million yesterday,
但是今天早上被转到一个境外账户去了
but it was transferred into an external account this morning,
联署人转的
by the cosigner.
有联署人的证件复印件吗
You got a copy of this cosigner's ID?
你的丈夫有婚外情
Your husband was having an affair.
就算不为了钱  你还是有动机
Even without the money, you had motive.
一般说来  我同意
In most cases, I'd agree with you.
为什么现在不同意呢
Why not in this one?
因为我也有婚外情
Because I had an affair too.
沃特金斯夫人  我们没发现
Ms. Watkins, we found no evidence
这一情况的任何证据
that would confirm that statement.
我另有一个电子邮箱
I have a second email.
他叫科林
His name was Colin.
是位医生
He was a doctor.
但我  我已经跟他分手了
But I-I broke it off with him.
电邮回复似乎能证明你的说法
Email correspondence appears to corroborate your story.
杰里米和我去年一直在为此纠结
Jeremy and I were struggling this past year.
他忙于工作  他有目标
He was busy with work, he had a purpose,
我却迷失了
and I was lost.
我不再是他娶我时的自己了
I wasn't the person he married.
我知道他有了
I knew he'd found...
别的女人  但是我们都够了
other women, but enough was enough.
我  我跟医生分手了
I-I broke it off with the doctor.
杰里米也发誓会放弃他的一时冲动
Jeremy swore he was through with his indiscretions.
我们  我们的游艇之行
We -- we were on the yacht
就是为了挽回婚姻
to rekindle our relationship.
你以为一顿浪漫的游艇晚餐
So you thought one romantic dinner
能够修复你们的问题
on a yacht would fix your problems?
不  但是
No, but...
我们总得有个开始
we had to start somewhere.
看着我的眼睛  告诉我你爱他
Look me in the eye, and tell me you loved him.
告诉我你不想撕烂他的脸
Tell me you didn't want to tear his face off.
你觉得我愤怒吗
Do I look angry to you?
我爱杰里米
I loved Jeremy.
现在还爱
I still do.
即使他的出轨对象是你至友吗
Even though he was having an affair with your best friend?
他  什么
He -- what?
即便我都会感觉杀得正当
Even I might consider that justifiable homicide.
我  我不明白  我
I-I don't understand. I--
妮可绝不会那么做
Nicole would never do that.
杰里米绝不会那么做
Jeremy would never do that.
很遗憾  凡妮莎  可他做了
I'm sorry, Vanessa, but he did.
已找到被偷车辆
Plate readers caught the 10-16.
搜索半径十个街区
Give me a ten-block radius.
给所有可能的目击证人看协查通告
Show any potential witness the BOLOs.
我们找到了车子  开始找嫌疑人  快
We found the vehicle, let's find the suspects, now!
各单位注意  各单位注意
All units, all units.
在58街和8街交界处发现嫌疑人车辆
Suspect vehicle found at 58th and 8th.
他们找到车了
They found the car.
我们得尽快决定如何处理沃特金斯夫人
We need to decide what to do with Ms. Watkins, soon.
指控她的证据都是栽赃的
The evidence against her was planted.
她没有金钱方面的动机
She dismissed any financial motive.
妮可和杰里米有外遇的事也刚刚知道
And Nicole and Jeremy's affair was news to her.
我觉得她丈夫不是她杀的
I don't think she killed her husband.
我赞同
I'm inclined to agree.
此案有颇多合理质疑
Reasonable doubt in this case abounds.
我们要投票表决么
Should we put it to a final vote?
说吧
Go ahead.
"重获清白"账户今早被提空
Innocence Now account was cleaned out this morning.
被凡妮莎提空了吗
By Vanessa?
不  联署人  亨利・沙恩
No, the cosigner, Henry Shain.
现在把照片给你发过去
We're sending a photo now.
亨利・沙恩就是杰里米・沃特金斯
Henry Shain is Jeremy Watkins.
凡妮莎没杀杰里米
Vanessa didn't kill Jeremy.
因为杰里米还活着
Because Jeremy is still alive.
杰里米怎么会还活着
How can Jeremy be alive?
我在水里看到了他的尸体
I saw his body in the water!
晚上很容易看错
It's easy to make that mistake at night.
他诈死
He faked his death.
他  陷害我
He...framed me.
尽管这种情况很令人遗憾
Despite the unfortunate circumstances,
但这可以证明你的清白
it does prove your innocence,
而且现在只有你能
but you're also the only person standing
毁掉你丈夫和他的新生活
between your husband and his new life.
我能让杰里米锒铛入狱
I could put Jeremy behind bars.
你是唯一的漏洞
You're a loose end,
我们相信杰里米下一步的目标就是你
and we believe Jeremy might come after you next.
我们得把你送出城
We need to get you out of town.
各单位注意  到56街和6街交界处东南角
All units, proceed to the southeast corner of 56th and 6th.
他们进大楼了
They're entering the building.
纽约警局  开门
NYPD! Open up!
凡妮莎  该走了  快
Vanessa, time to go. Come on.
举起手来
Hands up!
都不许动
Nobody move!
看住他们
Keep 'em up.
怎么回事
What the hell?
谁给的情报
Who gave us this intel?
有人打电话提供的线索
Someone called in a tip.
天鹅先生
A Mr. Swan.
各单位听令  即刻返回基地
10-2, report back to base, now.
知道警察是怎么找错地方的
Any idea how the police ended up on the wrong side of town?
摩根女士向我透露过
Ms. Morgan gave me a tip regarding
有一个地下赌博团伙
an underground gambling ring.
我只是想确保
I just wanted to make sure
警察能发现并捣毁它
the police discovered and stopped it.
所以你就把他们要找的越野车
So you left the SUV they were looking for
停在了那栋楼附近
near the building.
当然不是我
Of course I didn't.
是里瑟先生搞定的
Mr. Reese took care of that.
我是在履行公民责任
I was merely doing my civic duty.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
你要彻底抛弃原来的生活
You're leaving your life behind.
是会令人害怕
That's a scary thing.
你曾因为有人要杀你
Have you ever had to start over
而重新开始过吗
because someone was trying to kill you?
可以这么说
You could say that.
过来
Come here.
杰里米要我死  他会找到我的
Jeremy wants me dead. He'll find me.
凡妮莎  你很聪明
Vanessa, you're smart.
很坚强
You're strong.
如果我是杰里米  绝对不会想要追杀你
If I were Jeremy, I'd know better than to come after you.
也许我永远不会感到安全了
I don't know if I'll ever feel safe.
好吧
All right.
也许这个会有帮助
Maybe this will help.
已经上膛了
It's loaded.
谢谢你
Thank you.
为我所做的一切
For everything.
不客气
You're welcome.
你的  巴士马上要开了
Your, um, bus leaves soon.
是啊
Yeah.
可别错过了
Don't want to miss it.
多谢你让我旁听
I appreciate you letting me eavesdrop.
别客气
No problem.
不过我的午餐时间结束了
My lunch hour is over, though.
该回去了  免得卡梅伦调转枪头冲  我
Better get back before Cameron turns the troops...on me.
有什么不对吗  警探
Something wrong, Detective?
大多数人只知道手心出汗和心跳加速
Most people think that sweaty palms or an increased heart rate
是撒谎时身体的本能反应
are the only involuntary responses your body gives when you lie.
他们错了
They would be wrong.
她丈夫想要将谋杀罪嫁祸于她
Her husband tried to frame her for his murder.
也难怪她会生气
Can't blame her for being angry.
但她刮破那张照片时
Except she tore that picture
还不知道她的丈夫仍活着
before she knew he was still alive
也不知道她丈夫与妮可有外遇
and before she knew about the affair with Nicole,
当时她还说爱他
when she told me she loved him.
也许她确实爱他
Maybe she did love him.
我查了国际开发署的数据库
I've taken the liberty of revisiting the H-SAID database.
亨利・沙恩并非自己搞到护照出国
Henry Shain didn't obtain his own passport to leave the country.
他的妻子替他做的
His wife did it for him,
她也给自己搞到一个
and she procured one for herself too.
持有伪造护照的人不止杰里米一个
Jeremy wasn't the only one with a false passport.
凡妮莎给海岸警卫队打了那通求救电话
Vanessa made that SOS call to the coast guard.
她帮助杰里米诈死
She helped Jeremy fake his death.
凡妮莎从一开始就参与其中
Vanessa's been in on the plot from the beginning.
她和杰里米打算清空那个
She and Jeremy planned to empty out the accounts
所谓的慈善基金  并带着赃款出逃
of their so-called charity and run away with the spoils.
但杰里米背叛了她
Until he double-crossed her
并把自己的死嫁祸于她
and framed her for his own murder.
杰里米欺骗了凡妮莎  凡妮莎欺骗了我们
Jeremy deceived Vanessa, and Vanessa deceived us.
里瑟先生  凡妮莎说她爱她丈夫是在撒谎
Mr. Reese, Vanessa was lying when she said she loved her husband.
她协助他诈死
She helped him fake his death.
你还跟她在一起吗
Are you still with her?
她正准备上巴士
She's boarding her bus.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
凡妮莎没在巴士上  芬奇  她跑了
Vanessa's not on the bus, Finch. She's gone.
她知道自己的丈夫还活着
She knows her husband is still alive
而且还把他的死栽赃给自己
and that he framed her for his murder.
她恨他
She despises him.
她会杀了他
She's gonna kill him.
凡妮莎一直都是行凶者
Vanessa's been the perpetrator all along.
自从她丈夫陷害她后  她就一直在想谋杀他
She's been plotting her husband's murder since he framed her.
这表示她是有预谋犯罪
Which means her crime is premeditated.
-而我给了她凶器  -你什么
- And I gave her a weapon. - You what?
当时觉得是个好主意
Seemed like a good idea at the time.
找到杰里米  就能找到她
We find Jeremy, we find her.
他一定会离开纽约
He needs to get out of New York.
我知道一种交通工具无人会查
I know one mode of transportation no one's checking.
有情况要汇报吗
Anything to report?
我认为我的新搭档开始信任我了
I think my new partner is starting to trust me.
我还看到了她的男朋友
And I saw her boyfriend.
也许你认识
Maybe you know him.
妮可  我回来了
Nicole, I'm home!
期待是别人吗
Expecting someone else?
不  不  不  我只是
No, no, no, I just, um--
你怎么这么久才到
What took you so long?
你应该昨天就来跟我会合了
You were supposed to meet me yesterday.
不过今天更好
But today's better.
警察刚解封犯罪现场
Cops just released the crime scene.
我们可以走了
We are free to go.
你个奸诈的王八蛋
You duplicitous son of a bitch.
这都是误会
This is all a misunderstanding.
你知道我依然爱你  是吧  天使
I mean, you know I still love you, right, angel?
拜托  我们可以解决的
Now, come on. We can make this work.
离开纽约
Get out of New York.
把船扔了  重新开始
Ditch the boat. Make a new life.
陷害妻子谋杀后  这婚姻可就难挽救了
Hard to save your marriage after you frame your wife for murder.
你是什么人
Who the hell are you?
相关第三方
A concerned third party.
很高兴你找到另一位了  天使
So happy that you found someone else, angel.
真的  好样的
Truly. Good for you.
他不是我的"另一位"
He's not my "someone else."
他是我甩不掉的家伙
He's just someone I can't get rid of.
拜托  我们都心知肚明
Come on, we both knew that
这婚姻只是协议
our marriage was just a contract.
对我来说不是
Not to me it wasn't.
我以为  你是真心要一起离开
I thought you meant it when you told me we could disappear,
摆脱债务  重新开始
Get out from under the debt, make a new home,
我们重新生活
make a new life for us.
就我们
Just us.
我帮你诈死
I helped you fake your death,
向海岸警卫队作证看到你的尸体消失
Swore to the coast guard I'd seen your body disappear
好让他们宣告你死亡  一切如我们所计划
so they could declare you dead, just like we planned.
直到你陷害我
Until you framed me
卷走我们所有的慈善基金
and robbed our charity.
为了什么  跟妮可私奔吗
To what? Run off with Nicole?
也许你是对的  我们的婚姻只是协议
Maybe you're right, that our marriage is just a contract.
但如果这是真的  你欠我
But if that's true, you owe me.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
这么生气  刻薄
So angry, bitter.
你以前那么美
And you used to be so beautiful.
你让警察相信  我在游艇上对你枪击
You led the police to believe I shot you on a yacht,
然后将你的尸体丢下海
then threw your body overboard.
我做件所有人都认为我做过的事顺理成章
Who can blame me for doing what everyone says I already did?
做点什么啊
Do something.
你陷害自己的妻子谋杀
You framed your own wife for murder.
你骗过我  跑来杀自己的丈夫
You deceived me to kill your own husband.
我负责阻止坏事发生
I'm in the business of stopping bad things from happening.
我不确定接下来要发生的  算坏事
I'm not so sure what's about to happen is a bad thing.
正义号
里瑟先生  沃特金斯夫人怎么样了
Mr. Reese, how's Ms. Watkins?
不知道
Don't know.
不过你要打电话给海岸警卫队了
But you might want to call the Coast Guard.
还有  你欠肖100块
And you owe Shaw 100 bucks.
人人影视POI小组祝愿
轻伤不下火线的小麦早日康复
默默奉献的Alex生日快乐平安幸福